
[
   
      {
        "question": "A traditional story that explains the practice or beliefs of a people or something in the natural world",
        "choice1": "myth",
        "choice2": "ritual",
        "choice3": "oracle",
        "choice4": "fable",
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "Words or actions that are part of a religious ceremony",
        "choice1": "myth",
        "choice2": "ritual",
        "choice3": "oracle",
        "choice4": "fable",
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "A sacred shrine where a priest or priestess spoke for a god or goddess",
        "choice1": "myth",
        "choice2": "ritual",
        "choice3": "oracle",
        "choice4": "fable",
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "A story meant to teach a lesson",
        "choice1": "myth",
        "choice2": "ritual",
        "choice3": "oracle",
        "choice4": "fable",
        "answer": 4
      },
      {
        "question": "the custom of passing along stories by speech",
        "choice1": "oral tradition",
        "choice2": "drama",
        "choice3": "tragedy",
        "choice4": "comedy",
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "A story written in the form of a play ",
         "choice1": "oral tradition",
        "choice2": "drama",
        "choice3": "tragedy",
        "choice4": "comedy",
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "A play or film in which characters fail to overcome serious problems",
         "choice1": "oral tradition",
        "choice2": "drama",
        "choice3": "tragedy",
        "choice4": "comedy",
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "A play or film that tells a humurous story",
         "choice1": "oral tradition",
        "choice2": "drama",
        "choice3": "tragedy",
        "choice4": "comedy",
        "answer": 4
      },
      {
        "question": "The Greek people expressed their religious beliefs through _________",
        "choice1": "myths",
        "choice2": "drama",
        "choice3": "tragedy",
        "choice4": "comedy",
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "____________ a farmhouse Greek poet wrote the Iliad and the odyseey , epic poems about heroic deeds",
        "choice1": "Athena",
        "choice2": "Homer",
        "choice3": "Mario",
        "choice4": "Sparta",
        "answer": 2
      }
]
